[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以练习9和我们之前做的完全一样，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So exercise nine is that exact same exercise that we did before,
点击按钮和采样的那个。
the one with the clicking the buttons and the sampling.
但现在我要试着看看你能不能想出如何用CSP做这个，好吗？
But now I'm gonna try to see if you can figure out how to do this with CSP, okay?
所以我们休息20分钟。
So we'll take a let's say 20 minute break.
不是20分钟的休息。
Not 20 minute break.
但在这上面要花20分钟的工夫。
But a 20 minute work on this.
它比可观测的更具挑战性。
It's more challenging than the observables one.
更像是大脑弯曲。
It's more brain bending.
从我刚才给你的幻灯片中你应该已经有了大部分你需要的东西。
You should have most of what you need from the slides that I just gave you.
但当然可以随时联系并提出问题，
But certainly feel free to reach out and ask questions,
或者，如果您需要一些提示，请查看文件的固定版本。
or look at the fixed version of the file if you need some hints.